<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<!-- $Id: locallang_csh_ttcontent.xml 31215 2010-03-17 21:58:33Z francois $-->
<T3locallang>
	<meta type="array">
		<description>Contents of displaycontroller csh</description>
		<type>CSH</type>
		<csh_table>tt_content</csh_table>
		<fileId>EXT:displaycontroller/locallang_csh_ttcontent.xml</fileId>
		<labelContext type="array">
		</labelContext>
	</meta>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
			<label index="tx_displaycontroller_consumer.description">Choose the component that will transform the data into HTML.</label>
			<label index="tx_displaycontroller_provider.description">Choose the component that provides the data to display.</label>
			<label index="tx_displaycontroller_filtertype.description">Choose the type of filter to apply to the Primary Data Provider.</label>
			<label index="tx_displaycontroller_filtertype.details">
				"None" means that no filter is applied at all. Note that choosing this option will make any Advanced Data Filter defined to be ignored.

				"Detail view" makes the Display Controller automatically generate a filter based on the default GET/POST parameters used to define a detail view (tx_displaycontroller[table] and tx_displaycontroller[showUid]).

				"List view" works the same way, but for the default parameters used in a list view, which are related to browsing and sorting (tx_displaycontroller[max], tx_displaycontroller[page], tx_displaycontroller[order] and tx_displaycontroller[sort]).

				"Advanced filter" means that any Data Filter defined will be used. Data Filters should be used when the predefined filters described above are not sufficient for the given use case.
			</label>
			<label index="tx_displaycontroller_datafilter.description">This filter interacts with the Primary Data Provider. If defined don't forget to also check the "Advanced filter" radio button.</label>
			<label index="tx_displaycontroller_emptyfilter.description">Choose the behavior when the filter didn't return any condition.</label>
			<label index="tx_displaycontroller_emptyfilter.details">
				It may happen that the Data Filter returns nothing, for example when the GET/POST variables being looked for are not defined (think of hitting a search button without entering a search term).

				In such a case it is necessary to decide what should happen: either no data should be displayed ("Display nothing") or all the possible data should be displayed ("Display everything").
			</label>
			<label index="tx_displaycontroller_provider2.description">Choose the component that provides data to be fed into the Primary Data Provider.</label>
			<label index="tx_displaycontroller_provider2.details">
				Secondary Data Providers are generally specialized Data Providers that use some specific mechanism to retrieve some data. Most commonly they will return a list of id's (idlist-type data structure) which is fed into the Primary Data Provider to restrict the list of records it returns.
			</label>
			<label index="tx_displaycontroller_datafilter2.description">This filter interacts with the Secondary Data Provider. Note that some Secondary Data Providers don't handle filters.</label>
			<label index="tx_displaycontroller_emptyfilter2.description">Choose the behavior when the filter didn't return any condition.</label>
			<label index="tx_displaycontroller_emptyfilter2.details">
				It may happen that the (secondary) Data Filter returns nothing, for example when the GET/POST variables being looked for are not defined (think of hitting a search button without entering a search term).

				In such a case it is necessary to decide what should happen: either no data should be displayed ("Display nothing") or all the possible data should be displayed ("Display everything").
			</label>
			<label index="tx_displaycontroller_emptyprovider2.description">Choose the behavior when the Secondary Data Provider returns nothing.</label>
			<label index="tx_displaycontroller_emptyprovider2.details">
				The Secondary Data Provider is expected to make some specialized selection of records that are then handled by the Primary Data Provider.

				When the Secondary Data Provider returns nothing, it is necessary to decide what the Primary Data Provider should do: either do nothing either ("Display nothing") or proceed without restriction ("Display everything").
			</label>
		</languageKey>
	</data>
</T3locallang>
